Lesson 28.5 lb. too dear. Small boats loaded with wear sped to the great liner as she was entering the harbor.
第28.5磅，太亲爱的。小船进入港口时，装满了磨损的小船。
anchor: v.   停航下锚, deck: n.   甲板
Before she had anchored, the men from the boats had climbed on board and the decks were sun covered with colorful rugs from.
在她锚定之前，船上的人爬上了船，甲板上遮盖着五颜六色的地毯。
silverware: n.   银器, tempt: v.   吸引；引诱
Persia. Silks from India. Copper coffee pots. And beautiful handmade silverware. It was difficult not to be tempted.
波斯。来自印度的丝绸。铜咖啡壶。和美丽的手工银器。很难不被诱惑。
bargain: v.   讨价还价, disembark: v.   下船上岸
Many of the tourists on board had begun bargaining with the tradesmen. But I decide not to buy anything until I had disembarked.
船上的许多游客都开始与商人进行谈判。但是我决定不买任何东西，直到我下船。
assail: v.   纠缠
I had no sooner got off the ship than I was assailed by a man who wanted to sell me a diamond ring.
我没有尽快下船，这比我被一个想把钻石戒指卖给我的男人袭击了。
I had no intention of buying one. But I could not conceal the fact that I was impressed by the size of the diamonds.
我无意买一个。但是我无法掩盖这样一个事实，即钻石的大小给我留下了深刻的印象。
marble: n.   小玻璃球
Some of them were as big as marbles. The man went to great lengths to prove that the diamonds were real.
其中一些和大理石一样大。该男子竭尽全力证明钻石是真实的。
As we were walking past a shop, he held a diamond firmly against the window and made a deep impression in the glass.
当我们走过一家商店时，他牢牢地将钻石固定在窗户上，并在玻璃杯中留下了深刻的印象。
It took me over half an hour to get rid of him.
我花了半个多小时才摆脱他。
The next man to approach me was selling expensive pens and watches.
接近我的下一个男人是出售昂贵的笔和手表。
inscribe: v.   刻写，雕
I examined one of the pens closely. It certainly looked genuine. At the base of the gold cap, the words made in the USA had been nearly inscribed.
我仔细检查了其中一支。当然看起来很真实。在黄金帽的底部，几乎刻上了美国的单词。
The man said that the pen was worth $50. But as a special favor, he would let me have it for $30.
该名男子说这支笔价值50美元。但是，作为一个特别的好处，他会让我以30美元的价格获得它。
I shook my head and held up five fingers indicating that I was willing to pay $5.
我摇了摇头，举起了五个手指，表明我愿意支付5美元。
outrageous: adj. 出人预料的；令人不悦的
Justiculating wildly, the man acted as if he found my offer outrageous.
这个男人恰当地说道，好像他发现我的提议令人发指。
But he eventually reduced the price to $10. Shrugging my shoulders, I began to walk away when a moment later,
但是他最终将价格降低到10美元。耸了耸肩，稍后我开始走开
thrust: v.   硬塞给
he ran after me and thrust the pen into my hands. Though he kept throwing up his arms in despair,
他跑了我，将笔推到我手中。尽管他一直绝望地伸出胳膊，但
bargain: v.   讨价还价
he readily accepted the $5. I have him. I felt especially pleased with my wonderful bargain until I got back to the ship.
他很容易接受5美元。我有他。在回到船上之前，我对自己的讨价还价感到特别满意。
No matter how hard I tried, it was impossible to fill this beautiful pen with ink and to this day it has never written a single.
不管我多么努力，都不可能用墨水填充这支美丽的笔，直到今天，它从未写过。
World
世界